<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>twitter on codex</title>
    <link>https://gsajko.github.io/tags/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in twitter on codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gsajko.github.io/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Collecting and displaying data</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part2_filtering_out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part2_filtering_out/</guid>
      <description>Collecting training data Collecting data I collect Twitter data using a library made by Simon Willison - twitter-to-sql .
My first approach was to do it by myself: Twitter API is very clear, so it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too hard to just grab tweets with API and dump them into SQL? Right? It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem as a one-time-thing, as I usually had done in the past in jupyter notebooks. But if I would want to make something more robust - with proper testing etc it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a &amp;ldquo;custom twitter feed&amp;rdquo; project but a &amp;ldquo;Twitter API to SQL&amp;rdquo; project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom twitter feed project, Part 1: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/custom-twitter-feed-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 10:15:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/custom-twitter-feed-part1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is an introductory post about the project I&amp;rsquo;m making. I&amp;rsquo;m in process of reading Machine Learning Bookcamp Book by Alexey Grigorev . The main &amp;ldquo;meta&amp;rdquo; concept behind this book is the idea, that the best way to learn Machine Learning is by doing projects.
In parallel, I follow Applied ML course by Goku Mohandas .
I will try to incorporate things I learn from both of those sources while doing this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to research stuff using Twitter</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/posts/use_twitter_for_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 19:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/posts/use_twitter_for_research/</guid>
      <description>Key to this method - follow lots of opinionated people. I follow many people - more than 600. There are many ML experts. So if I&amp;rsquo;m researching what methods to use, what algorithms, or just want to learn about a subject I&amp;rsquo;ll use Twitter first for that.
Using search Let&amp;rsquo;s say I want to learn how to do &amp;ldquo;topic modeling&amp;rdquo; on a dataset made of tweets. I just use search, remembering to check &amp;ldquo;People you follow&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to avoid distractions while using Twitter</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/posts/avoid_twitter_distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 18:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/posts/avoid_twitter_distractions/</guid>
      <description>TLDR: use uBlock Origin block stuff with uBlock Origin uBlock Origin is a browser plugin, which I use mainly as an adblocker. But you can also use its &amp;ldquo;picker mode&amp;rdquo; to block custom elements from a website.
I used it for example to block out &amp;ldquo;Trends for you&amp;rdquo;
But it was not working correctly every time.
I tried this: https://schleiss.io/fixing-twitter-design-with-extension/ but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work.
So I found an even better solution:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
