<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>custom_feed on codex</title>
    <link>https://gsajko.github.io/tags/custom_feed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in custom_feed on codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 19:15:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gsajko.github.io/tags/custom_feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Testing Data with Great Expectations</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/testing_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 19:15:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/testing_data/</guid>
      <description>Why Data Validation If you use python, I hope you use some tool to help you validate and test the code you are writing, for example pytest, or pylint. But we should also test validity of the data.
For example, missing values could be very problematic for some models, so it&amp;rsquo;s better to recognize errors in our dataset before we load them into a model (or even before we start pre-processing)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom twitter feed, Part 3: Displaying Tweets</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part3_displaying/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 18:08:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part3_displaying/</guid>
      <description>Displaying and reviewing tweets. I query tweets, I filter them out. And how to &amp;ldquo;serve&amp;rdquo; them? Best solution would be this In theory, this could happen, as Jack Dorsey seems to be &amp;ldquo;for it&amp;rdquo;. Second, the value of social media is shifting away from content hosting and removal, and towards recommendation algorithms directing one’s attention. Unfortunately, these algorithms are typically proprietary, and one can’t choose or build alternatives. Yet.
&amp;mdash; jack (@jack) December 11, 2019  But I had to look at other options in the meantime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom twitter feed, Part 2: Collecting and Filtering Data</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part2_collecting_filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 16:43:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/part2_collecting_filtering/</guid>
      <description>Collecting training data Collecting data I collect Twitter data using a library made by Simon Willison - twitter-to-sql .
My first approach was to do it by myself: Twitter API is very clear, so it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too hard to just grab tweets with API and dump them into SQL? Right? It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem as a one-time-thing, as I usually had done in the past in jupyter notebooks. But if I would want to make something more robust - with proper testing etc it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a &amp;ldquo;custom twitter feed&amp;rdquo; project but a &amp;ldquo;Twitter API to SQL&amp;rdquo; project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom twitter feed, Part 1: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/custom-twitter-feed-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 10:15:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gsajko.github.io/projects/custom-twitter-feed-part1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is an introductory post about the project I&amp;rsquo;m making. I&amp;rsquo;m in process of reading Machine Learning Bookcamp Book by Alexey Grigorev . The main &amp;ldquo;meta&amp;rdquo; concept behind this book is the idea, that the best way to learn Machine Learning is by doing projects.
In parallel, I follow Applied ML course by Goku Mohandas .
I will try to incorporate things I learn from both of those sources while doing this project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
